yeah I mean I had a lot of times when I
just automatic my system by mistake you
know and like but every time I came back
stronger so I had like three times of
that iteration of those iterations but
if you know rmrfs three times
[Music]
I never in my life have I done that so I
need a little more context
[Music]
yo knockly welcome to the Pod man thank
you thank you very much happy to be here
yo so okay I want to start out this
episode we've got a bunch of questions
for you and I'm hoping we can get to the
Recon Secret Sauce in this episode see
if we can get them to Spill The Spill
the Beans but I wanted to start with so
uh a while back you know I thought I met
nogly for the first time or the first
talk to nagley at a live hacking event
but
um when I when we started chatting
nagley sent me a message or told me that
he had sent me a message back in what
was it let's let's pull up the DM here
it was January of 2021 which actually is
not that long ago when you think about
it
um saying like hey
can you look at my Recon flow can you
like validate and then he just drops
this like massive X mind like mine of
like pretty much the sort I mean it
literally has all of the source code
like curl and like all the all the
commands that you're running and I'm
looking through here and I'm like wow
this guy is actually let me see what I
said I said um dude that looks freaking
sick nice work brother
so I mean at this time knockly had you
done much hacking at this point or were
you just like kind of like building out
your recon framework yeah so I didn't do
much click on at the time I just did
some deal do you know get some
computation after my account get some
private invites I think I got like only
one thousand dollars
two years and like four months ago and
it just looked to validate some of my
stuff with you know the top hackers at
the time and just chill to it all
because I don't want you my DM to get
lost in your a lot of Andre diem so just
here is my code yeah no and it looked
amazing and I was I have to say even at
the time I can tell from the way that
I've responded to you like I was like oh
oh dang you know because we get as the
top hackers I'm sure you know this now
not wait you know being one of the top
hackers yourself but um you know we get
a lot of GMS that says like uh you know
hey can you help me with this can you
like validate my this and that and the
other thing and a lot of time it's like
really like basic stuff and you're like
okay but then he drops this whole like
mind map with like all of the source
code all of the bash that he's running
and I'm like dang this guy's pretty
legit and then we had a conversation you
know following that of like hey you know
you might want to architect it like this
you know actually so the advice that I
gave you is hey I don't really see like
a message broker in here
um and and so I mean did you ever
Implement a message broker or are you
doing some other way to like connect all
the parts to your system
yeah not really I mean there are two
types of automation hackers either you
build the whole devops infrastructure
with message broker and containers and
stuff like that I went to the mall you
know just bare scripts while Loops con
jobs Axiom and you know to the the easy
route we could say yeah the I mean
that's kind of like I think we talked
about it a little bit at the live
hacking events but um
that's I mean that's what a lot of the
top hackers do you know you'd imagine
that these people have like everything
written in Rust like distributed across
all the things but when you really talk
to people it's like dang there's a lot
of like
bash going on here and like like really
Scrappy systems built up so I uh I just
thinking back on this I I I'm so glad
that you know I responded to this
message and we got to have that that
early interaction because look at him
now he is okay hold on I I've prepped
this and ugly hold on he is the newest
million dollar hacker whoa whoa you hear
the cheering
okay nice
so congrats on that man and actually so
I mean you said you had made maybe a
thousand dollars on hacker one at this
point this is January of 2021
so you went from mating having made a
thousand dollars in January of 20 20 21
to being the latest million dollar
hacker is that right yeah I barely made
any money on 2021 so in like only in
2022 only last year it was like since
look for Jay you just it just went off
okay so log4j was a big pivot point for
you or what yeah I mean getting some
look for jazz you know two hours after
it was published on Twitter just got my
nuclei scripts running you know and it
got a lot of like 10K bounties and stuff
like that for me from programs it was a
good Leap Forward nice man wow that's
cool so man I feel like log4j was not
that that long ago so you you've really
you know you really scaled up quick so
okay my goal for this for this session
is to you know try to get some of the
secret sauce out of out of knobbly try
to see how much of of his uh you know of
his techniques we can I can pull out
um so okay so you said for Jay was one
of the one of the big things what other
kind of what other kind of
vulnerabilities are you poking around
for in ugly
yeah I mean it was a lot of supplement
takeovers you know and names
gcp all those kind of stuff you know
back at the time it was to get a lot of
these now it's like
three to five very like 1K 2K a month
sure sure but just generic
vulnerabilities you know not nothing
really really spicy at the moment I used
to in Vegas last year I tried to build
my ec2 automation but it's so much hard
work I know the two packets are doing it
but I'm not really in that game because
it's so hard to maintain you need
thousands of accounts and there's a lot
of money in it I know a lot of the top
markets are doing it but I'm just okay I
give up on that I don't know I don't
know so when you say ec2 uh you're
talking about ec2 IP takeovers right
Yeah so basically you have a rotation
script on your account try to claim IPS
and then you check your record date and
you see if any DNS name points so
they've selected IP and if you get a
match then okay
you've got your recon data and then you
know you've got that all built out and
then you're you're generating ec2
instances or ec2 IPS checking the IP and
seeing if like any of these DNS records
that were out there were pointing to
that IP and that IP address is getting
reused and passed on to a different
customer right yeah gotcha wow yeah
that's that that sounds like a lot and I
know I I actually dabbled in that a
little bit and I had it for a little
while I had it you know generating a
couple Grand a month off of off of
findings but
um I think you know not too long ago AWS
sort of implemented some sort of rate
limiting rate limiting surrounding that
right
you know they're trying to ban your
accounts mostly and then you need new
credit cards new phone numbers I mean
it's a whole operation oh my gosh just
too much time I mean I I get a lot
that's definitely definitely a lot more
uh yeah that's involved in going into
that for sure yeah
um yeah ec2ip okay so you've got that
you've got so here's one of the problems
that I ran into
um and I I think nogly and Joel you
probably know this but for for the
audience I'll talk a little bit about
this so at the beginning of my of my
buck Bounty career I was kind of like I
was doing mostly just well I guess at
the very beginning I started off
building reconnaissance based stuff and
I was like oh man this is really hard
you know and then I started doing just
like hands on the keyboards hacking and
and like diving deep into the
application finding some stuff and then
I was like okay you know I feel like
I've got a little bit of a better grip
on this now let's go full automation so
um one of the things so I built out this
whole system I probably put thousands of
hours into building this system and uh
and it worked great for a couple years
um but one of the biggest problems that
I ran into was getting and especially
it's especially important for these
things like NS takeovers and for like
anything related to subdomain takeovers
um is getting a clear picture of the DNS
configuration of of an organization or
an asset in practically real time right
because like as soon as anything changes
you need to be the one to know oh hey
this just went from you know NX domain
to serve fail right now and I need to to
pull that asset so I mean how are you
how are you trying to get what it what
kind of tools are you using to get that
clear up-to-date picture of the DNS
configuration of of a you know set of
assets
um I just use the normal open source
tools I have some I modify them a little
bit maybe for some input output for
easier so it will be more convenient for
me but I didn't develop any you know
Innovative grass kind of thing because I
didn't find it like I didn't need it I
didn't feel like I needed it and I used
a lot of benchmarking with more
challenging I mean it was just fun to
compete with them we have like a yeah a
small Channel fast you know just bashing
each other just comparing of that yeah
and it's very nice to have this kind of
competition you know and uh
I know firsthand that you thrive off of
that
so that's cool yeah I think I think
having you know Joel and I were kind of
talking about this last week having
hacker chats you know having sharing
with other hackers and talking to other
hackers like you know a lot of people
would say hey man you need to keep your
secret sauce secret and that sort of
thing but like you'd be surprised about
how much better of a hacker you you you
know become when you start sharing and
starting having conversations with other
hackers
yeah I believe that 80 of the bugs of
the you know the good bugs that you
submit to programs it's either
automation or collaboration I mean the
collaboration you get a lot more
insights better findings I think that's
like the bigger part of the picture when
you see quality bugs and programs yeah
um so I guess this was another route
that I wanted to go down so I know just
in your in the history of Natalie
becoming you know what he is today that
there was a big a big pivot point was
that was you starting this thing called
Bug Bounty Hunter's Guild and could you
tell me a little bit about that and like
how that helped you improve as a hacker
yeah so I spoke and on May of June of
2021 I started getting a little you know
10K months with my automation it's after
coming takeovers and then I spoke a lot
with docs in the motion on different uh
Discord chats you know just private chat
they would copy paste the text to each
other and then why won't we just you
know have a snare go up and just check
with each other and you know drop some
stuff some Twitter threads some
interesting things so I just started
this back Mountain Hunter's Guild it was
like five of us maybe or six and then
just invited more people that we saw
over over the leaderboards on the tweet
and just you know to speak in a more
control Channel and it was great success
not only for me but for other hackers
they made connections with each other a
lot of collaborations have gone from
that point so it was very good for a
while now as for every slack channel
it's decreasing in the in the engagement
over time some other mini groups located
but it was very good for a year there
and now it's mostly for DMS yeah and I
feel like you know at some point you
it's hard to keep engaged men in those
in those sort of communities but I think
it's cool that as you you know as
probably the fastest zero to a million
hacker that I've ever seen
um you know I think it's really cool
that a part of that was building a
community at the same time right that
building a community is like its own
you know full-time job but you know you
built a community and you were you know
kind of fostering growth in other
hackers and like communicating with
other hackers and you know treating
trading techniques and stuff like that
with other hackers while you were
building out your automation framework
and getting getting to that magical
number of 10K a month on on automated
automated stuff so I I think that and
they're the full-time job as well yeah
yeah well and of course right on top of
that you actually have a full-time jobs
which you just recently quit right
uh seven months ago I think that was it
has it already been seven months since
you pulled the plug on that time flies
oh my gosh man so you quit that and you
know I guess you started you started
Shockwave then yeah so you want to talk
a little bit about that
yeah it's my own starter I mean I took
my services into a product because it's
more scalable and I see a lot more value
that I can bring to companies insights
when I also connect to the internal DNA
stuff and the cloud security posture
tools then yeah the biggest task is to
find all the sub domains so if you can
collect it also from the inside I can
run my automation continuous monitoring
it more recently and the point is for
companies to have this you know
automated hackers attacks them every
time and also to have a platform for
them to collaborate like to do a
challenge is to invite researchers so
instead of giving you DNS Zone file you
know or text files with all the records
let's just invite you to that ASM you
will see all the assets you can
collaborate and chat with others leave
notes and then you could pull you know
good findings and that's like the goal
of the of the collaboration and the
automation tool for companies
wow that's awesome yeah that's kind of
what you were talking about last week
Joel with like with the DNS records
giving the DNS host you know Zone Zone
files yeah there we go I couldn't I
couldn't get it out giving the Zone
files to hackers to you know try to
eliminate that security by OBS security
thing right
yeah exactly I mean you see too many
companies do it where they're just hide
stuff behind like a weird complex domain
or like a bunch of sub domains that
nobody can find and
yeah it gets tricky for sure and it's a
I mean and on top of that the platform
is designed around I mean you're giving
them additional Recon data too like
ports and and you know server
fingerprinting and that sort of thing
right yeah everything that I would do
with my automation scripts is just
taking a good I mean getting out of the
command line and also getting the
additional insert I can give them nice
that's very cool man and I remember you
know we were at a live hacking event I
think it was Vegas and you showed me the
the no it was it was Barcelona
um and you showed me the progress that
your developer was making on the front
end of the GUI and that thing is pretty
man so so talk to me a little bit about
about like how did you go about putting
a GUI on this thing and like you know
yeah talk to me about that yeah it's
very hard I mean either you develop
everything from scratch and then you
need a lot of developments but a single
developer in Israel is like 150 200 000
yeah and you I wouldn't I won't just
pull all my money into it before
validation stuff like that so I took a
development and I took a bootstrap
template you know a tablet I can style
form and then sure you know I pay I paid
some money for a designer to make it
look nicer and more with the brand
identity and then just developing it
like I mean I have a vision of you know
attack selfies I've seen a lot of
products I know what we is what we want
to look what we want to see so just you
know going from that point is low level
nice man that's that's really cool so so
one of the things that kind of stood out
to me there was that you said that you
hired a designer
and so I know I know you have a coder
but you also had a designer is that
correct or is this a same person yeah so
another book like I hired the designer
for a small gig and then I hired another
one for to do some LinkedIn post
templates and you know ever since I
needed another person let's just grab
someone painful to show Steam for the
project and then move on you know to
guide it like a not stopping yeah I I
dude I love that I love the use of
Delegation because like that is one of
the things that I struggle with the most
is like handing off things that I am not
good at to people that are good at them
and then just paying the money you know
like it's it's so it's such a good
efficiency piece
um so yeah great to hear that and and I
also love that you know that you did
hire an individual designer aside from
your coder and gave your coder you know
for the front end some some you know
some template some design to some docs
to work with because
um you know the coder the coders aren't
always necessarily the best designers
and and vice versa right so I when I
tried to bootstrap my own yeah bootstrap
see that's that's a nice little pun
there when I try to bootstrap my own uh
front end my front my own GUI for my my
thing it was total crap because I mean I
can write front end code but I can't
design front-end code and so
um yeah that was that was really smart
to go about it that way for sure
have you ever noticed like any struggles
between getting the designers and the
coder stores together like sensor just
sort of both random people
and yeah so I always like keep my
developer I create more tickets for me
in GitHub and I really like detailed for
him like very slowly like he doesn't
need to speak with me I give him a
um an assignment and after two weeks he
just speaks with me I mean we don't need
to I don't need to talk with him daily
you know about stuff but I also had some
bad experiences with another developer I
tried to like move everything to react
from bootstrap which sounds like a good
idea it can protect from exercises it
will be more smooth you know the website
and stuff like that but it was I mean it
didn't make sense because I developed
like in two different lifespans he
developed a front end for feature that
we didn't develop yet and then so it
didn't make sense so I lost like ten
thousand dollars for it but yeah never
mind we'll make it up
foreign
I love that I love that that
entrepreneurial Spirit like yeah like I
feel like I would get so caught up on
that like uh you know nah why did I make
this terrible move or like how do I like
still stick to my guts on you know going
to react even when it's not working so I
think I think uh I think that's a really
good indicator of someone who's going to
be successful in the entrepreneurial
industry is that ability to you know
quickly adapt not not trip over the
failures not trip over the missteps and
uh and continue rolling and I'm sure
that's the same thing that kind of got
you into the into the space where you're
at with with Recon too is like you know
start going down a path be like Ah
that's not going to be the right
approach and then you know adapt and and
change so that's really that's really
good to see yeah
um all right let's let's get back to the
doc here Joel you got any questions you
want to shoot them or should I just go
off rapid fire
yeah so I mean you talked a little bit
about like your recon and like you know
doing bug Bonnie and stuff but how did
you what was like your path before bug
bunny what led you to like do bug bunny
in the first place and be interested in
security and all that
yes so I started studying in an open
University in computer science because I
always like like computer science but I
was in the Army and the the final year
of my offices
like in my military service I was in a
cyber security department and then I was
exposed to a lot of cyber security
information not really Hands-On more
like in like to make some slides about
attacks and stuff like that you know but
I got into the the world of knowing
attacks and stuff like that and then I
started I took a call some Stanford it's
called Web security cs253
it was it's kind of advanced course
about JavaScript cookies exercises and
so on but it was really good for me
knows one practical course just to learn
about some attacks it has some Labs so
it's very high I mean if I will watch it
again today I will probably learn new
stuff again but this was like a nice
course for me to start with and then I
mean that Bounty it's it's good because
you don't need anything from the company
you just need to open build and you know
start hacking so that's what got me into
like investing in that kind of field and
not like going to internal pensive
Network pen testing which is it requires
you to have some sort of relationship
with the company beforehand
yeah no that's interesting and yeah
gradual well and then like what made you
want to eventually shift away from that
like what you just talked about like
it's Bugatti is nice because you don't
have to have a relationship with the
company but now as you've gone through
bug binding now you actually are like
creating relationships with companies
you're doing internal pens that type of
stuff so what what Drew you away from
bug Bunny and back towards that other
stuff
and yeah because I mean back volunteers
don't really know how how you will do
next month so I mean you don't really
You can predict if you will find bugs
and over the course of Mines I see that
I find less bugs I mean it's of course
many many more people are trying to do
what I do and they are succeeding in it
so I see that I get less bucks on my
Automation and that's why I decided also
to build my product and I know what I
could get from companies with a
relationship that will make them
actually more secure I mean they're
using board as like mine I mean they're
using it external success management
probably you know all the folks and 100
companies that we're hacking but still
the focus there it's not really the
focus that we find the box with and
probably malicious actors because they
are more focused on outdated softwares
or nift cves and all of the stuff which
are not really exploitable and that's
the big difference between us and them
so I decided to maybe try to go over
that route as well and but also of
course background I'm still doing it and
grinding what's there
gotcha so how much time would you say
you're spending doing like manual like
looking finding new bugs like prodding
at a specific product versus just sort
of running it through your whole
automation Suite that already exists and
seeing what it returns this is the
question man I love this yeah yeah I
barely do any manual hacking and I hate
it because I can't focus I can't find
the program to focus it and it's so
disturbing I mean it's live working
events I will always find a bug somehow
I don't know why because there is a
competition and there is a you know
there is the grind that is the the
environment but actually doing manual
hacking these days I barely managed to
do it because I can't focus on the
program I mean if I will find a good
program I will manage to authenticate to
it I will do it but I can't really force
myself to do it that's that's so that's
so interesting because like that I've
mostly interacted with you in the Live
Hack and we've done a lot of live
hacking events together so you know it's
not an insubstantial amount of
interaction but the the uh you know I've
mostly interacted with you in a live
hacking event front and that was one of
the things things I was going to ask you
about was like I feel from my
perspective I see you in live hacking
events right which is when you're like
in the zone you're like locked in you
know you can really focus because of the
competition and I noticed that you know
you're one of the rare exceptions uh of
people that do both Recon hardcore Recon
and also hardcore hacking like he is in
the authenticated app finding you know
the the you know sea surfs and stuff
like that they where you have to be
authenticated to find it
um as well as also doing this Mass
scanning and like look at this weird
asset I found you know in the middle of
nowhere
um and so that that's really interesting
to hear you say that you know your
normal approach is actually mostly just
the Recon and you just kind of pull that
out of nowhere for the live hacking
events
uh yeah I don't know why I mean I wish I
could find some programs you know to
just go all in on them for a year and
make like 100 200 000 yeah I know it's
possible probably if I would focus maybe
if I would have a friendly competition
with someone but it's hard I mean if
anyone manages to manages to figure out
how to incentivize it like to make us
Focus as a collaboratory program it
could be very good to hear yeah I think
I mean that's something I've been trying
to figure out forever it's I have the
same the same problem where it's like
live hacking event something about like
timing and pressure and just opportunity
makes it so ripe for finding good new
bugs and then even if you were like to
come back a month later and try and hack
the same program you might have like no
luck or you might just like not have
that same kind of energy or motivation
or like
creativity or anything like that and I I
see that all the time where I'll be like
I don't really want to hack on that
comes up in a live hacking event I'll
spend like a month hacking on it and
I'll be like that was a lot of fun and
then yeah I'll like either come back
then I'll be obsessed with it or I'll
like never want to hack on it again yeah
I feel like I do the same thing even
with like the post event uh stuff
because I'm always like you know at the
end of the event you still got a list of
things that are like ah these things are
kind of sketchy like I I should
definitely go back and poke at these a
little bit more but then like you know
I've got to take a break after the live
hacking events too right so you take a
couple days and then you come back and
you're like man this target is like
awful you know and you don't you don't
think that when you're at the live
hacking event so it's definitely
something really cool that uh you know
the platforms have going on for him
there
and it's always you know it's it's
mostly not new Scopes it's just it's
usually the same Scopes and the most out
in programs yes yeah that's what
everyone to know
yeah so on that topic like you hack on a
lot of different programs a lot of
different Scopes all that kind of stuff
do you take notes in any type of
structured way like how do you keep
track of stuff is it all within
Shockwave or
yeah so it's very hard to keep notes he
puts it in a DMV to me is what he does
oh oh just add me to that I'll help keep
track yeah just shoot every piece of
information to everyone that I can but
on the last event on the epic games
um could we say the name I think we
could if not I'll bleep it you're good
okay
so we actually I collaborated with a
space raccoon and Alex Wilson so we use
some sort of a markdown collaborative
just to shoot everything on the markdown
so everyone could see I still don't have
anything on Shockwave by still
developing so we could leave notes on
assets you know then you could if you
want to check credentials if you want to
say specific things to a HTTP server
then you could really easily see it and
you know communicate with it with each
other because it's very hard I mean I
don't know how do you how you
collaborate I know Justin is usually
like soloing and then just getting all
his leads and then you know trying to
collaborate on site or and we got very
nice bags on Austin as well on site on
the couch
right out of nowhere that was so fun
dude right in front of the fireplace
like yeah so it's very hard I mean to
maintain all the notes and of course
it's very useful but I'm not doing it
very well at the moment yeah I feel like
I mean Joe I don't know what you think
about this but like I don't I don't know
a bug Bounty Hunter that says anything
different than what nagley just said
like pretty much everyone's like yeah
you know I really should take notes but
actually I'm garbage at this and so like
I don't know do you do you I mean do you
take notes Joel do you know anybody who
takes like really meticulous notes
um meticulous notes I I don't think I
know of anybody who takes them
personally I don't either take like
meticulous notes I just take notes
sometimes and it depends on the
structure it's like sometimes I'll just
do like a Google doc or a Google sheet
or something and I'll just dump stuff in
there
if that's like a good format
um other times if I'm just hacking alone
I might just have a text file in like vs
code that I just leave on my other
monitor and I just sort of dump thoughts
and like bullet points
um I don't think I've really gotten any
further structure than that I know a lot
of people
um like to use notion and stuff that's
pretty cool I just I don't really want
to like get to the point where I'm
getting distracted by formatting and
writing my notes and all that kind of
stuff yeah while also trying to hack
right I want it to be something that's
functional yeah exactly yeah
down on this thing and then I like throw
it in the garbage the next day I'm
holding a yellow I forget we're on a
podcast medium sometimes I'm holding
just a yellow like legal pad and I just
you know I just write like exactly what
you said Joe just like write random
ideas down there and then I just throw
it away which is so like yeah you know I
do that with the sticky notes you've got
the sticky notes right there so it's
just like I don't know I feel like
that's that's I feel like maybe that's
something we could do better and it
might be better when like I have find
some really good like AI note taking
thing where I can just like brain dump
from a voice and have it like Auto
generate some cool notes or something
like that but um for right now you know
I haven't seen well a lot of a lot of
really talented book bounty hunters
listen to this pod so let us know on the
comments on Twitter
um on this on this episode drop if you
if you guys find if you guys really do
take good notes or if you found a really
good system for that and if it's really
added a lot of value because
um from right now from what I can see it
hasn't really done a lot for for most
other hackers so
yeah yeah something that allows you to
like I don't know maybe there's a
product somewhere like a product idea in
your summer right but it needs to be
like something that's like easy to use
you can just sort of dump like any type
of data in there and like just needs to
be easy to like manipulate and format I
don't I don't know what you know but
like something like that at some bridge
between like a physical notepad and like
a Google doc I'm not so we used we use
Hakim dito
it's just
when everyone is editing and stuff in
there yeah I think you actually sent me
something on this at some point yeah
probably yeah yeah yeah when we wrote
the report for the collaborate this
looks pretty good man yeah I think this
might be this might be something that we
need to
you know stay on top of because yeah as
long as it's got real time and marked I
mean that's pretty much like the two
things you need in real time and
markdown and I think it does have that
so that's pretty that's pretty baller it
might have to that is pretty much more
when I do collaboration
cool yeah okay cool yeah so that's a
that's a pretty good uh we just sort of
came up with a little note note-taking
strategy I might have to try that out
um
what would you say
the like biggest thing that you've
learned over the last you know three
years especially from the escalation
point starting at like January 2021 like
what what are the biggest changes that
you've made between like then and now
that are like large structural changes
to your hunting process
um mostly you learn a lot by trying to
find bugs and not finding them then you
know what to skip you know I mean
probably at the beginning people would
look at CSS files and you know and just
try to find bugs on them because but
there shouldn't be any bugs on css5 so
it must need to grind a lot everything
on Twitter I digest into my mind just
trying to to figure out if there's
anything interesting just you know just
hacking and seeing all the new
techniques that come and networking is
very important you know to speak with
people to know how to control your
temple sometimes when a program is is
giving you some you know not the Bounty
you you expected or some other stuff
that you can't control then if you can
control it you can control it and so
that's some good stuff in order to take
into into into concept
it's hard man uh when you when you get a
really disappointing thing in the in the
beginning but I think uh I think like
you said trying and failing is some of
the best ways to grow and that's so hard
to tell newbies in the space because
they're trying to think about you know
whether they've got what it takes to
succeed in the space and you know if you
just tell them yeah just keep on failing
and failing and failing and failing then
it's like
you know what are they going to do with
that but I mean that's how it is so yeah
yeah
so how do you find most of your like
news stuff on Twitter or like how do you
ingest like new techniques new types of
bugs new stuff to add to your automation
yeah mostly Twitter and I have a feed to
my email to my spam email about all
every new nuclear template because there
are too many but just see if there's
anything new with my tech stack so I
could just fight it over sometimes
people reach out to me and when they
have a zero day risk assessments
configuration and you know they just
they tested all the programs and now
they tell me so I tell them okay you can
just give me the software don't give me
the PLC before I find anything and then
when I find new stuff you collaborate 50
50. so it's good it's a good model for
me for them it's win-win yeah so that's
also people just reaching out to nagley
with zero days yeah I mean to be honest
I've done that and that's kind of like
nagley's one of my go-to guys for that
is you know just toss them toss them a
uh identifier for the you know
vulnerable version or whatever and he's
like yeah I've got like 60 of these
which ones you know and and so
um that's always been then one year
later another one pops you know yeah
exactly and I mean like still to this
day and that's another thing you know
that you do with the grafana bug right
I'll just call it out because everyone
yeah everyone has already seen that bug
but I mean knockly still messages me I
think the last message you sent me was
like three weeks ago of like hey another
one popped up here we go again bro you
know and uh and so I always appreciate
that and so that actually leads me to to
wonder how many of your bugs are
like collaboration versus you know your
your own stuff do you think you know
you've got a decent like what's that
ratio of like people come coming to you
with bugs and versus your own stuff
uh yeah I don't know I had one very good
collaboration with Hixson from from
yesterday hack if you if you know him
it's very good and we made a lot of
stuff one time with the mochan we were
in a Paris attacking event yes we hack
we just sit in a restaurant we drink
lemonade you know and then he just told
me about the one time he got a lot of
takeovers from from a Vendo and then I
told him oh why won't I just sign up to
that Vendo and then we made 64k out of
that simple lunch
sometimes I get collaboration sometimes
not but I don't know I mean it's either
I had a lot of bugs with collaborations
with each other
wow that's awesome man that's awesome
um are there other are there areas like
specific topics that you feel like
you're really lacking knowledge and you
want to spend time like learning and
expanding
yeah probably mobile and you have your
previous idea I didn't I didn't hear you
please why do we have an episode for you
yeah two even
yeah so actually listen to the episodes
in the gym all the time but this one
maybe I don't want to listen to in the
gym because I want to install stuff or
see some stuff you know so for the next
live hacking event I also I might need
some mobile knowledge so that's an area
of the time I'm looking to go further in
then that's probably it I guess nice
cool well you can always hit me up dude
um Joel is like I always hit Jola from
mobile stuff and he's just like the
wizard of the Bible with that and if he
there's the bonus here's the bonus thing
that makes collaborate with Joel so
great is if he doesn't know then you
have just sparked him you have nerd
sniped him to go figure out what it is
because I'm gonna get instant nerd
Snipes yeah he's not he's not the kind
of guy that should be like oh yeah not
really sure
see ya no idea no let me know what you
find out yeah no it's gonna be like huh
not sure and then you get a message five
minutes later hey I think it might be
this 10 minutes later I think it's no
maybe it's this you know and it just
goes down that hole so I always
appreciate that I mean not everyone not
everyone can do that but I it's always
it's great when um when you know you've
got another brain like Joel's to work on
it with you and kind of you know work
work to the end of problems so I think
that's one of the reasons I enjoy
collabing with Joel so much and ask him
to do this podcast is you know we we
really it well to put it concisely he's
nerd sniperable well I mean it's funny
because we've had all these
conversations about like collaboration
and stuff and so much of pug Bounty like
really good bugs ends up being
collaboration yeah I think a part of
that is just that it takes a lot of
different perspectives and smart Minds
to attack a problem from a different
perspective to come up with those
different ideas right so
um you know you're sitting in a in the
coffee shop in France and you're
chatting with this this other hacker
like Hey I'm we find this he's like oh
yeah you know I did this thing and then
you have this unique idea right why
don't we just sign up for it and like
those types of things like it might seem
obvious but like it just takes that
extra perspective and that extra like
experience that you have had to maybe
you've done that in the past right and
it might work on this target or maybe
you were just you know you saw a video
or something and you you thought oh
maybe that'll work here and so that that
amount of combined experience and that
combined like context altogether is what
I think like really makes the in-person
collaboration I mean it doesn't have to
be in person but like collaboration in
general just like really elevates your
bugs yeah I mean you don't have to know
everything I tweeted like two years ago
like a phone book you know I have my own
phone book to to message anyone you know
I have a friend of Vishay so he doesn't
do much about this but he knows how to
find exercise everywhere I mean no
matter the Target no matter how so it's
very you know convenient another sub
domain another endpoint here this
exercise you know this kind of stuff so
it's I mean I have a phone book for
anyone I will get child from a certain
all kind of thing that's developed on so
that's it's also very nice if you don't
you can't learn everything you know so
just play to each one's
strengths yeah for sure and and I think
in addition to that everyone
doesn't you know each individual person
has their own holes in knowledge as well
and those also can be helpful this is
what I tell my mentees a lot too is like
you know you bring A New Perspective to
this target that I don't have because
I've got trained eyes and I've got
experience you know looking at this
thing before and think ah you know
that's never been vulnerable in the past
so it's never going to be vulnerable
again and sometimes you know these these
newer people don't have that so they
start going down this path and then and
then you know a lot of times they'll
show me stuff they'll be like hey this
feels kind of odd right and I'm like
yeah I've seen that like a thousand
times and I have never seen it do that
actually and so you know it's really
just to encourage any any of the new
people that are listening here is like
you know you you think you can always
ping you know an experienced hacker and
be like hey you know uh is this is this
you know something that I should look
into or not something I should look into
and sure there you know a lot of times
we're gonna all come to the same
conclusion but there's there's a lot of
value in going through that process and
understanding because we miss stuff you
know Joel Miss stuff snuggly Miss stuff
and and you're you're the listener you
you have a unique perspective that we
don't have and that will lead you to
find bugs and that and that's okay hold
on hold on I gotta calm myself down a
little bit here because I'm getting more
height this is how at the live hacking
events is going off I'm going off man
are you ready for this here it comes no
but this is how at the live hacking
events like you said Joel they're
hardened targets and we always always
drop crits and destroy the target like
in without fail and and so it's like you
know time and time again so many eyes
have been over that but each individual
person brings A New Perspective and you
know can drop new crits or find new
Pathways where where exploitation can
happen so anyway sorry I I went went
full uh you know bug Bounty evangelist
there but you guys you know you see that
you see what I'm saying right yeah yeah
I mean I think you could raise some
great points like first like the whole
trained eyes thing that happens to me
all the time and like I'll think like oh
there's no way that could happen
or like you'll somebody will describe me
but you'll describe a book to be just
we'll be talking and be like hey I have
this weird Behavior over there are you
sure and like I'll immediately like
think like I'm not sure about that and
then like it's it you know it ends up
being the case I think the most recent
case was this import thing and like
JavaScript there's like this import
function and it's like the whole trained
eye thing is like you know if you just
get too comfortable like being like oh
I've seen that before I'm pretty sure I
know how this works like
that that new perspective of coming in
and being like I have no idea how this
works is like great to just
expand your like your mind a little bit
you know just like think more about the
problem think is this possible and try
those different things that you wouldn't
have ever tried before yeah okay all
right we we I I totally agree with that
and I could Vibe on that [__] all day
but I'm gonna rain this back in I'm
gonna get us back to the dock I'm gonna
get us back to that optimizing the time
with knobbly here yeah and then Joel and
I can just rant about that [__] on a
different episode
but um okay so this is one that I had on
there and this is uh I'll I'll explain
okay so let me just say the question
first
what I want to ask is how much of your
time do you spend coding versus hacking
ugly and I think I know the answer to
this but this was my problem with the
Recon game you know and and I think we
talked about this actually at a live
hacking event not believe but my problem
was that I really enjoy
going up against a hard hacking problem
and solving that and when I was in the
Recon game I felt like I spent 80 of my
time and maybe it's because I'm a [__]
programmer but I felt like I've spent 80
percent of my time coding in much less
of my time actually exploding so I mean
what does that ratio look like to you
and how do you feel about that ratio
yeah I mean I had a lot of times when I
just I remember left my system by
mistake you know and like but every time
I came back stronger so like three times
of that iteration of those iterations
[Music]
listen I never in my life have I done
that so I need a little more context I
mean one time the last time it was like
two years ago maybe and it just I ran
action and I wait for the results and
then I can't log into my to myself I
mean it just password not working and
then somehow we train our memory I don't
know why I don't know how and then I
since then I modified my Axiom and I
never updated it for like one year and a
half so my accent is like not updated
because I can't risk having rmrf on my
system but now I do this is what I have
today 20 000 commits on Gita because I I
backup my code and my record data every
30 minutes so that's like what I did
because of that but it's a lot of bug
fixes a lot of it's like you said a lot
more time to fix the codes and the
trivial stuff that are not working
instead of hacking or sometimes you add
a domain and which is one million sub
domains 10 million sub domains and it
blows up your automation so there's a
lot of edge cases that you need to take
care of when you want to have the ones
in order to work I mean I Can Fly for a
week now and it nothing will happen so
that's takes a lot of time to twist that
level yeah it absolutely does and and I
mean do you I mean obviously
we're all hackers but do you do you
consider yourself I mean from a
day-to-day basis do you think you spend
more time coding than hacking
I'm not I'm I mean most of my stuff
already coded I mean all the titles play
for the best scripts or the security
mindset every time I see new feature it
can be automated I will code it but
mostly I'm researching today you know
just seeing new stuff that pop up
hacking I mean I don't have any much
more to contribute in the coding part I
mean I don't know how to code Django for
my system back and in front I wish I
know but like that's it's hard even with
3gpt it can help you a lot but it can't
help you with the whole architecture you
know of uh of everything but yeah I mean
literally converted all my best to
python for example I mean just copy
paste okay I mean you need some
Integrations but that's very it's very
good use case if you want to transform
to another language it's not good for
complex architecture back and foreign
wow so do you have plans to integrate AI
like into your product at all or what's
the plan yeah so I have a simple
integration when you add the report so
we take your title the severity and the
end point then I could I could guess
what you want to report this references
with AI so it's like if you report a
gray log log for J you will see also
they I will know the references for the
patch and stuff like that so that's like
a cool feature and another good feature
I mean Auto triage it's something I plan
if you if my my clients will make a VDP
page or bbp on their website and they
will submit a bug then I will give it a
keyword let's say of a
you know all those kind of stuff that
you don't want to see you could just
very easily have an AI that detects it
so you know for those kind of stuff Auto
triage I think it's very good for
literally finding new bugs I don't have
any use case yet with Automation and so
JavaScript files is probably very good
to analyze JavaScript files yeah but I
don't see any I mean it can't make my
stuff faster for now so in that font
mostly JavaScript files I think can be
it's very good to analyze it
yeah JavaScript files would definitely
seeing someone spin something up that
like the problem is you know they're so
long you know and so yeah you need to
make a lot of things yeah and you know
you can't just dump all of that into
chat
so easily and even when you do you're
you're hitting you're probably you're
definitely going to hit the chat GPT
token memory limit you know where it
doesn't remember the stuff you put in
from the beginning so it's not going to
be as simple as like just using the API
dumping all the pieces in and saying hey
tell me about what I just dumped in
there I think it's got to be a little
bit more complex but when it is
that is going to be helpful that is
going to be really helpful because
nobody likes reading minified JavaScript
it makes our eyes bleed we know
um so yeah yeah that would definitely be
cool cool
so Natalie you you travel a lot right
like you you're always going to Live
Hack events I always see you on planes
and all that kind of stuff right is it
yeah is that pretty accurate yeah I mean
yeah it's having like 10 to 10 live
walking events last year and I think it
started with Dubai Pele Danville Austin
Vegas Singapore
Barcelona coping again and then Florida
this so it's like it was like 10 I think
maybe that's crazy I think that's a lot
of plays yeah I've done that I've done
10 in a year as well and that is uh that
is like that is a grind that is a grind
for sure
um when you're on planes are you hacking
are you coding are you bug fixing are
you sleeping podcasting what do you what
do you do on planes yeah I mean I buy
the wife you know most of the flights to
the US like 15 hours so I invite them I
tried to code a little bit but usually I
will just you know and watch some
Netflix and if I buy myself business
maybe I'd like to sleep but I it's how
to you know to commit in playing to code
or to to do some stuff but um yeah I
mean it's really hard to do it on a long
flights
got it got it so would would you say a
lot of your money goes to business class
upgrades that's where that that million
is going so fast he's flying business
class across the ocean yeah yeah not
much I mean mostly stream economy
sometimes I allow myself to fly you know
in the Emirates I mean I had to
experience it once and then why not I
mean I don't spend my money anywhere so
I should spend it on something
cool yeah no that was actually one of
our questions was like what where does
all the money go because like billion
dollar hacker yeah falling out of
control right like what's going on
yeah so I mean I'm very conservative I
could say I just all my money now is
mostly it's on money market fund it's
like five percent a year very solid and
I can catch it out whenever I want and I
didn't buy any real estate or any you
know major stuff it's mostly paying for
my expenses when I'm traveling eating in
restaurants you know and you know for
the flights and hotels and yeah maybe in
the future you know I buy some you know
some cool stuff
saving up for the private jet we we have
a different idea of conservative because
nagley's like flying and he says most of
the time it's premium economy I wouldn't
go down to Super basic economy like Hey
listen you gotta spend 15 on a plane you
gotta you gotta draw the line somewhere
okay yeah it's true no I don't know man
I like I don't know they're just not
that uncomfortable for Me Maybe maybe
it's because I'm like like perfectly the
average you know height Dimension you
know sort of guy and so everything was
designed for me which is really nice but
um but like I don't know I sit in this
this seat and then I open my laptop and
I do some stuff and then I I mean even
on the flights to Japan it's not that
bad so I I don't know I I uh I I never
invest in the in the business class I
mean do you Joel I feel like you're the
same for the dimensions I I definitely I
definitely do sometimes like it depends
I think for me the line is like anything
over
eight or nine hours I'll probably
upgrade to at least premium economy and
depending on the price of the upgrade I
might go to business yeah just because
like uh that's like a full day of just
like sitting in a chair like next to a
bunch of people just like you know
he told me yeah you know we're in cavali
flies all the time so he told me one
hundred dollars for an hour it's what
you should pay if you want to fly
business I mean maximum for the argument
so it has like very specific formulas
they if you want to calculate if you
will if it's worth it or not you know
it's kind of interesting though like he
when you say it like that even I don't
really like
you know you're paying a hundred dollars
an hour to be transported across the
world
you know like in slightly more Comfort
it's actually not that I mean that's
pretty good you know like I don't know
so yeah it depends on perspective right
like I I think the most expensive
business upgrade I ever did was to
Singapore and that was like yeah yeah
but it's like for for me from SF even
like from West Coast it's like 19-hour
flight there yeah it's like
19 hours like what do you do in a in a
tube for 19 hours like I want to recline
that's what I want to do okay I don't
know now that that makes sense I I think
I don't know maybe maybe we'll see
someday especially we're gonna convince
Justin's flying first from now on
upgrade check my flight upgrades really
quick Clickety clackity
um but uh but also you know hey United's
got a bug Downey program and I will say
uh you know just to be fair because this
is how we do it here I haven't had the
best experience with the United bug
Bonnie program
but the bounties are great you know if
you get if you get the bounties the
bounties are really good
um as far as like how far those points
go and especially if you're you know you
know how to get and now I've really
shown my my conservative side if you
know how to get the super economy saver
deals then you can get some really good
um you know Redemption rates for those
points so they do they do yeah they do
tax you on them which is a little bit of
a bummer if you're a U.S citizen but
this is another hack you heard it here
and it's not tax advice
you can just write them off as well if
you use them for business so
um you know that's that's kind of the
way I've been I've been dealing with it
and who knows maybe I should I should
Splurge a little bit more and go uh and
go business sometime I'll have to check
that out yeah yeah well while we're
talking about flights Andy and Carol you
mentioned um
but he has like a calculator and stuff
he also has that site um seats.arrow and
that's like all around points yeah yeah
he has this website called seats.arrow
and it like it looks for basically like
last minute like Airlines like to sell
off their their empty seats at like
basically mile only rates for like it'll
be like 40 000 miles plus a hundred
dollars or ten dollars or something and
instead of like a full-size first class
ticket and if you are you know looking
for a flight you have the points for it
you can usually snag those up like
pretty last minute like for pretty cheap
um yeah and so he has a whole like
website to track all that stuff so if
you're hacking on United and you have a
lot of United points and you're looking
for a good way to spend them seats
probably a good way to find some of
those flights this is his site yeah
no way dude way to go this is awesome
seats.air so
s-e-a-t-s dot a e r o seats dot Arrow
yep
huh pretty dope
yeah Ian flies a lot he's uh he's a cool
dude we should we should try and have
money or something sometime because that
man is uh he's doing a million things at
the same time yeah for sure and I didn't
I didn't know idea that he could program
as well this is this this website that
very much gives me
um what's that guy's name is it like
links.io or something like that links.io
yeah hold on I don't know if I we're
getting we're getting off the hacking
topic here but there's this guy links.io
that does uh AI
let me see if I can find it
I can't find it right now but he does
like AI um he does nomad list that's the
that's the name list and uh his name on
Twitter what is it levels that's what it
was yeah thank you and I just if you
look at all of his sights he talks about
how like he just really like quickly
spins stuff up and like he has a PHP
endpoints they're chosen like he's there
yeah and that's so cool like if I was
gonna be a Creator I would definitely go
down this route and also you know he
talks about how he just iterates with
all he just does jQuery and bootstrap
and in PHP on the back yeah and he just
pushes out these amazing sites so this
seed stat era really gives me that sort
of Indie levels levels
it's a it's another one of those like
experienced like train dies versus
amateurized thing like if you're if your
eyes get too trained you start to like
if you say I want to write one of these
I would absolutely spend way too much
time trying to trying to make it perfect
and like nice for the user and whatever
instead of just
keeping it simple and just iterating on
it yeah
yeah
um all right we are approaching the hour
mark here let me see what else I got on
the list uh if I don't have too much
else then we might have to go into those
um vulnerabilities that we were talking
about
um okay actually
let me ask this so you know you said the
tech stack is largely
Dash so let me just I'm just going to
check this this fact so bash you've got
um you've got you know you're wrapping
uh the actual other other tools right
and then you said you have Django for
for
um that's for Shockwave but you weren't
using that at all before it was just
yeah I'm still not using it for my uh
for my you know my automation for black
Bounty just python bash Axion digital
ocean
text files
I don't know man I just feel like you
know even when I was using back in the
day I used [__] because it was just
really handy but like I was kicking
myself for not utilizing like you know a
real SQL database you know like MySQL or
something like that with you know all
these different relational queries you
can do trained eyes yeah and you know
boom he just goes straight for the bash
and txt files and a lot of them
yeah yeah crap he says oh yeah for the
database
I don't know if you've ever heard of
this it's pretty unique it's called grep
yeah oh my gosh that's good
um all right cool well you know what
there we can't get anything out of them
from the stack because there's nothing
in the stack it's just yeah I almost
like and can't get more simple than this
he's like telling us how it all works
he's like what do you want from he's
like actually just breathe back I'm
um
okay so let's talk about the uh let's
talk about the reports a little bit um
I'm gonna go ahead and let's see so yeah
why don't you start off with the web
cache uh deception one not Glee so
anyway let me just explain this to
audience real quick so you know when the
guests come on we want to have we want
to have them talk about reports rather
than our reports that we are quickly
burning through on on the podcast here
so we're gonna have Natalie talk about a
web cache deception uh phone that he
found on chat GPT which totally blew up
on Twitter and then also a uh a ssrf
from a live hacking event that we've
done recently that we will not share the
name of the target for an ugly yeah
otherwise I will have to bleep it but
yeah so hit us with the webcast
deception one man
yeah so lately you know
um we're having a kind of this code with
Sam Carey and well and just you know
looking for landing targets once every
few days to hack so it was jgpt day they
just introduced the the plugins and it
was very exciting so I just said why not
look at it for a little bit and with
that and then I never actually I mean I
found cash deception sometimes on live
hacking events in Denver I found it and
I think on another one but I never tried
the bypasses you know so I saw I saw
some stuff how it Powers how it
authenticates you with the judging
between stuff like that and then I saw
this API endpoint it just gives you your
JWT and all your authentication
authenticated data and I thought well
let's see if it cashes I mean I read
some write-ups I know that you if you
can add static files and the end from
still you know functions the same and
you could still get a hit so you have a
battery so just you know just tried
test.css and oh I got a hit from the
cash server it means there's something
in so it was pretty straightforward just
shoot him an email in four minutes he
answered to me I wish they had a bad
body program it's probably like 10
minutes yeah four minutes oh my gosh
dude if we could get that sort of
response in like actual bug Bounty
programs that'd be crazy and then let
alone you just shot this guy an email
yeah I know that guy was he was managing
one of the biggest programs for
background the guy who manages open AI
in VDP now really I bet they will have a
background program soon so probably I
lost like 10 to 25 000 uh if it was a P1
but uh well the exposure and you know
the the publicity was very good for it
and it was a very fun bug you know to
find a bag on the early days of AI and
those kind of systems it's very cool and
there's a lot of webbacks to find all
those stuff for sure yeah wow dude this
uh this tweet really really blew up so
you did get some good exposure there
um for those of you that are at a
computer listening to this if you go to
the description we'll link the Tweet
um that we're talking about uh or you
can just look up not only on Twitter
um but which you should be doing anyway
to follow him at naguinogly uh
dude you were you were actually made me
really wonder so you mentioned like most
of the time you see something you don't
try and bypass it do does your whole
automation system and all the alerts do
you have it alert you for like
non-findings if that makes sense like
stuff that is weird but needs probably a
little bit of extra like human effort to
fully exploit or do you just sort of
just cut your losses with that stuff and
yeah I have some kind of automation that
allows me for new interesting domain it
just became publicly accessible and
stuff like that so it's not a finding
but with a quick look I could probably
see if there is anything here to explore
or not I wish I could you know make
something with faf and director wolf was
like take most common Ten Thousand Words
okay but it's very much it's hard acid
but you could find some good stuff with
it if you keep monitoring your stuff
over and over
gotcha nice so I'm looking at I'm
looking at this tweet and
um I don't know what is it like the
fifth fifth tweet down or whatever you
talk about receiving the
um cf-cash status response
um set to Dynamic right so normally
um when you see Dynamic you know that's
like a bummer right because it's it
knows that you're not you know that this
is changing content but it's it's still
an interesting thing that that indicates
you that there is some caching mechanism
in place right so then you know from
there you can sort of
uh you know he he for any of you that
aren't super familiar with why we have
reception you should absolutely go find
this tweet because he does a brilliant
job of of outlining how it actually
works and you even show the default
cached file extensions from cloudflare
in there which I do not have a list of
before so that's um that's really
awesome and it might even be cool to
even build some automation that tries
all of these endpoints or tries all of
these extensions and on every single one
because maybe they fixed like the one
for PNG and jpg or even WAFF but like
some of this stuff like you know what is
it dot zst I've never used extensions
over there yeah have you already turned
this into an automation or is this just
sort of like a one-off yeah it's hard
because everything is to end point it's
very hard I didn't figure it out I know
some people did but using GAO and having
you know a small amount of output
eventually it's very it's super hard
problem I mean to find apis on
authenticated and stuff like that so I
didn't really do any automation with it
well this is a really impactful one so
then after you put you know test.css at
the end it cached the response and then
from an unauthenticated perspective
anybody could come hit slash test CSS
and we would find your your uh auth
access token right yeah I tried it with
Joel We went with VPN and just you know
he went to my link then I got to JWT and
now I see all the interactions you know
so what you're saying is Joel has your
access token to chat GPT no no no no he
has mine oh no
Joel you fool I know I'm doomed he's
gonna steal my bugs yeah
oh my gosh that's great um Okay cool so
let's let's hit uh that ssrf then so
this is a really fun bug I'll intro it
for it for you nagley
um this was a bug that nogly and I and a
couple other people found at a live
hacking event 312 recently and um
yeah I think it's just a really good
example of collaboration taking things a
little bit a little bit further and also
just like a pretty
you know when you think about ssrf as a
volume type you think about hitting
internal internal assets and stuff like
that but there are some other uh things
that you should be keeping your eye out
for which we'll learn about in just a
sec so not really hit us with the
details on that one yes it was the final
day of the on-site event so we were
hacking for like two weeks for this very
very small web app and I just you know
someone taught me Jonathan Bowman if you
know him he's a doctor and he's a happy
as well so he just taught me how to use
the belt active scanner I never used it
before because it's never it never
finishes so I I just said why not why
not just fire it over my my Recon data
and it found the most weird S7 that no
one could ever found because for every
endpoint that I called it just tried to
end slash HTTP and you know the pair of
collab the URL and you will never you
would never drive on the end for that it
actually found it so when I opened my
computer at night just you know when we
were hiking late night in your home and
then I just thought oh what is this
weird external DNS interaction alert and
then we saw we actually add sslf on the
instance and when we when I looked at my
collaborator so we saw there is a JWT so
it was only external it was like you
could say blind but when you point to
yourself it included ability for super
admin and then you know we try to to see
how further how far can we take this
vulnerability too so we no one would
ever find it if we you weren't just
fasting some weighted endpoints will
pass and it's one of the best the most
critical bug in the events yeah man that
was such a fun one because it literally
like you know we were like okay and when
you see where it injects the payload it
literally injects you know normally when
you've got necessary if it's like okay
you know clearly a URL it goes here or
like a host name goes here and then we
can manipulate that this was just like
slap it at the end of the URL with https
included in everything and it would just
yeah hit that so that was that was kind
of nuts actually I I still don't
understand fully how that happened on
the back end but
um yeah having that Bearer leak is was
really was really huge and I've seen
this at a couple different life hacking
events as well so whenever you get a
call back on your verb collaborator
don't just you know freak out and you
know start thinking about hey what what
sort of internal stuff can I hit
double click into the request read it
thoroughly look at the user agent look
at the authorization look at any other
headers that are going along there that
might indicate to you what kind of
softwares are being used or what kind of
additional information is being leaked
and you might end up with the best bug
of the event like not only here so oh
wait hold on yeah this is another
opportunity for me to do
[Applause]
amazing amazing
yeah it's super interesting that burp
active active scan stuff because that's
one of those features I also like never
touched there's a lot of features in
verb that I just like they either didn't
work for me one time and I just stopped
using them or I don't fully understand
the best way to use them and I just like
skip over them and yeah I'm gonna have
to I'm gonna go learn how to use that
yeah so give us the rundown I mean what
did he teach you there in ugly
I mean I think it broke for me again
because it doesn't finish for me today
as well but it actually just showed me
that you can antique some stuff and then
it won't run forever you know
the scans like it you know like all
right should I Like You Know download
this whole Javascript file and analyze
it for six hours button yeah you don't
want it to look for for all the stuff
the zip zipping Dom exercise you know
some stuff you want to focus on the
status
it's like to help you you know it's the
most critical and the nice stuff and you
wanted to finish this is the most
important part yeah so creating your own
custom scan profiles that's a that's a
pro tip right there so you get more
value out of out of burp because I think
you know it's a little bit designed for
taking a long time and someone who's
just really like you know the the red
team person for their for their company
or whatever and it's just gonna let this
scan run for forever and uh and you know
as a bug Bounty Hunter we've got a
little bit of a different agenda there
so creating your own scan profiles
that's a good that's a good takeaway
there
um all right we are just over the hour
Mark
um I since we finished the reports I
think uh that's all I got Joel you got
any anything you want to pick Natalie's
brain about
that that was it I mean this was awesome
yeah just getting to hear your insights
about how how you approach things and
how you set things up and how your whole
Recon works and all that kind of stuff
and it's really exciting to see you
building it into a product too yeah for
sure you got anything you want to uh you
want to share here at the end anything
you want to promote
um no I will promote the podcast you
know if you listen to this podcast you
should listen to the podcast and and
it's not it's not very good to generate
lead form from the ones who already
listening
what a guy what a guy she's using his
his 15 seconds here at the end to
promote the the podcast I will say
though I will say you know we were we've
you know from time to time we'll be like
we'll come on here and we'll be like hey
you know please you know subscribe on
what the heck sorry something
we'll say you know subscribe on YouTube
or whatever but one of the biggest ways
that podcasts grow uh and we also talk
about the hacker chat so it's really
relevant is Word of Mouth you know so
drop if you you know do us a solid do
give knockly some pay for his for his uh
his trip on here and share the podcast
uh in your your hacker chats or your
discords or whatever and or even tell a
friend in person and because nogly was
so kind to shout out the Pod instead of
shouting himself out I will say
definitely keep an eye on Shockwave
um his his uh his startup that he's
doing
um you can find it we'll link it in the
in the description of the podcast as
well and uh yeah I think I think that's
about it that's the Pod yeah
that's right all right sweet thanks for
listening everybody peace thank you very
much